seamlessweb.com 2015-10-26

# GrubHub Holdings : Privacy Policy

**Updated and Effective April 16, 2014**

We are concerned about privacy issues and want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below). This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with privacy and the Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through this website (seamless.com), the related mobile sites and mobile application(s), and selected other domains (the "Sites"). Except as indicated below, this Privacy Policy does not address the collection, use or disclosure of information by any of our affiliates or by other third parties on any websites other than the Sites. As used in this Agreement, "GrubHub Holdings," "we," "us," and "our" shall mean GrubHub Holdings Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates.

By accessing and/or using the Sites, you agree to all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, do not use the Sites. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and without prior notice. If we make a change to this Privacy Policy, it will be effective as soon as we post it, and the most current version of this Privacy Policy will always be posted under the Privacy Policy tab of the Seamless website. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we may notify you. You agree that you will check out this Privacy Policy periodically. By continuing to access and/or use the Sites after we make changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. You agree that if you do not agree to the new terms of the Privacy Policy, you will stop using the Sites.

For individuals in the UK, you should be aware that your personal information may be transferred to and stored in the United States. We abide by the Safe Harbor framework agreed to by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union (EU) with respect to Personally Identifiable Information collected by Seamless Europe, Limited and transferred to us in the United States. Please review our Safe Harbor Privacy Policy for further information.

## 1\. What Types of Information Do We and Our Third Party Service Providers Collect From You?

**Personally Identifiable Information** (or " **PII** ") ") is information that identifies you as an individual. In order for you to take advantage of particular opportunities provided through the Sites (for example, to use the services offered on the Sites), we may require that you furnish PII. We and our third party service providers collect your PII, such as your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number or other payment account number (including the three (3) or four (4) digit validation code for your credit card), date of birth, when you voluntarily provide it to us or when your employer provides any such PII to us.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** (or " **Non-PII** ") is aggregated information, demographic information and any other information that does not reveal your specific identity. We and our third party service providers may collect your Non-PII, including information about the device you are using in accessing and/or using the Sites, information from referring websites, and your interaction with the Sites. We and our third party service providers also may aggregate PII in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the Sites, for example, by using PII to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code. Additionally, we and our third party service providers may collect Non-PII such as your employer's department code and expense code when provided to us by your or your employer.

**Cookies and Other Technology** A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent by GrubHub Holdings to your Internet browser and stored on your computer's hard drive, and that delivers information about you and your activity on the Sites. Pixel tags and web beacons are small graphic files that can function in various ways (such as allowing us to track how you view an email that we send you, and track your activity on the Sites) and are commonly used in conjunction with cookies. We, our third party service providers and other third parties detailed below under "How Do We Use Information Collected From You?" may use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other similar technologies to better serve you with more tailored information and facilitate your ongoing use of the Sites. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline the use of cookies. To learn more about cookies, please visit the third party site <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. Some browsers allow you to indicate that you would not like your online activities tracked, using “Do Not Track” indicators (“DNT Indicators”), however we are not obligated to respond to these indicators. Presently we are not set up to respond to DNT Indicators. This means that latent information about your online activities may be used by us to improve your use of our Sites, but such usage is consistent with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

**IP Addresses** are the Internet Protocol addresses of the computers that you are using. Your IP Address is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). Your IP Address is identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you visit the Sites, along with the time(s) of your visit(s) and the page(s) of the Sites that you visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many web sites.

## 2\. How Do We and Our Third Party Service Providers Use Information Collected From You?

**Personally Identifiable Information**. We and our third party service providers may use your PII and any third party PII that you may provide, as applicable:

  * to fulfill your requests, e.g., to allow you to order food through our restaurant partners and have it delivered to you or to provide you with information that you request.
  * to fulfill your purchases (e.g., to process credit card payments in connection with your food order).
  * to customize content on our Sites (e.g., the restaurants that will deliver to your location).
  * to send you important information regarding the Sites, such as certain changes to our terms, conditions, policies and/or other administrative information. Because this information may be material to your use of the Sites, you may not opt-out of receiving such communications.
  * to inform you of products, programs, services and promotions that we believe may be of interest to you.
  * to permit you to send messages regarding Site-related content to a friend through the Sites. If you wish to use this feature, you may be required to provide us with, and we may use, your friend's email address to facilitate your sending of such message. By using this functionality, you affirm that you are entitled to use and provide us with your friend's name and email address for this purpose. We will not to use your friend's PII for any purpose other than to allow your message to be sent and/or to troubleshoot any issues with respect to the sending of your message, unless we disclose such other purpose to you at the time you provide your friend's PII to us.
  * to permit you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions (collectively, "Promotions").
  * for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our website, improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**. Because your Non-PII does not personally identify you, we and our third party service providers may use such information for any purpose. For example, we work with third parties for the purpose of advertisement delivery on the Sites including online behavioral advertising (“OBA”) and multi-site advertising. The Non-PII collected about your visits to the Sites may be used by third parties in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These third parties may also set cookies to assist with advertisement delivery services. If you would like to obtain more information about the practices of some of these third parties, or if you would like to make choices about their use of your information, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

In addition, we reserve the right to share your Non-PII with our affiliates and with other third parties, for any purpose. In some instances, we and our third party service providers may combine Non-PII with PII. For example, on your personal profile page, we may display your user name (first name and last initial), "member since" date, total number of ratings and reviews, the ratings and reviews you have posted and their date(s) of posting, and the date range of when you last ordered from a particular restaurant. If we do combine any Non-PII with PII, the combined information will be treated by us as PII hereunder (as long as it is so combined).

**IP Addresses**. We and our third party service providers use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, diagnosing server problems, and administering the Sites. Please note that we treat IP addresses, server log files and related information as Non-PII, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. Accordingly, in general we may use and disclose IP Addresses for all the purposes for which we use and disclose PII.

## 3\. How Do We and Our Third Party Service Providers Share Your Personally Identifiable Information With Others?

We and our third party service providers may disclose PII:

  * to our affiliates, including [Seamless Europe, Limited](http://www.seamlessuk.co.uk/), so that they also may use such PII for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. GrubHub Holdings is the party responsible for the management of the jointly-used PII.
  * to provide services such as payment processing, website hosting, data analysis, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, e-mail delivery services, and other similar services, to enable them to provide services.
  * to third parties such as attorneys, collection agencies, tribunals or law enforcement authorities pursuant to valid requests in connection with alleged violations of GrubHub Holdings terms of use and service or other alleged contract violations, infringement or similar harm to persons or property.
  * As required to fulfill your purchase (e.g., to our restaurant partners to enable them to fulfill your order).
  * to identify you to any person to whom you send messages through the Sites.
  * to third parties sponsors of Promotions (irrespective of whether such Promotions are hosted by us), or otherwise in accordance with the rules applicable to such Promotions. You should carefully review the rules, if any, of each Promotion in which you participate, as they may contain additional important information about our, a sponsor's and/or other third parties' use of your PII. To the extent that the rules of those Promotions concerning the treatment of your PII conflict with this Privacy Policy, the rules of those Promotions shall control.
  * to an affiliate or other third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy and/or similar proceedings).
  * as we believe to be appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations and/or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety and/or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you and/or others; (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies and/or limit the damages that we may sustain; and (h) for recordkeeping purposes.

## 4\. Other Important Notices Regarding Our Privacy Practices.

**Forums and Profiles**. We and our third party service providers may make available through the Sites certain services (for example, message boards, chat functionality, "profile pages" and blogs) to which you may be able to post information and materials. Please note that any information you provide in connection with such services may become public, and may be available to visitors to the Sites and to the general public, including without limitation the Ratings and Reviews that accompany many restaurant listings and the comments section of our blog posts. We urge you to exercise discretion and caution when deciding to disclose your PII, and/or any other information and/or materials, on the Sites. NEITHER WE, NOR ANY OF OUR THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, NOR ANY OTHER PERSON OR ENTITY DULY AUTHORIZED BY US AND/OR BY OUR THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS, IS OR SHALL BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY USE BY ANY UNAUTHORIZED PERSON OR ENTITY OF ANY PII YOU DISCLOSE THROUGH THE SITES.

**Third Party Sites**. Except as expressly set forth herein, this Privacy Policy does not address, and neither we nor our third party service providers are responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of other websites and/or any third parties, including without limitation any of our affiliates and/or any third party operating any site to which the Sites contains a link. The inclusion of a link to a third party website on the Sites does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us or by our affiliates. Please note that your access and/or use of any third party websites, including by providing any information, materials and/or other content to such sites, is entirely at your own risk.

**Security**. We and our third party service providers use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect PII under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please do not send us sensitive information through email. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is not secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the "Contacting Us" section below. (Note that if you choose to notify us via physical mail, this will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem.)

**Unsubscribe**. If you do not wish to receive marketing-related emails from us, you may unsubscribe from receiving them by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any of those emails.

**Changing PII**. You may review, correct and/or update certain elements of your PII by adjusting your preferences in the "My Account" section of Seamless.com. We and our third party service providers are not responsible for altering PII from the databases and/or other records of third parties with whom we and our third party service providers have shared your PII.

**Retention Period**. We and our third party service providers will retain PII for the period reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**Note Regarding the Use of the Site by Children**. The Sites are not directed to and/or intended for use by individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that such individuals not use the Sites and not provide PII through the Sites.

**Disclaimer**. If you choose to access the Sites, you do so at your own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations. We may limit the availability of the Sites, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area and/or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. By using the Sites and submitting any PII, you consent to the transfer of PII to other countries, such as the United States, which may provide a different level of data security than your country of residence provides.

**Contacting Us**. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at [privacy@grubhub.com](mailto:privacy@grubhub.com), or please write to the following address:

> GrubHub Holdings Inc.  
>  Attention: Privacy Team  
>  1065 Avenue of the Americas, 15th Floor  
>  New York, NY 10018
> 
> Tel: (800) 905-9322, option 2 

Please note that e-mail communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly you should not include credit card information and/or other sensitive personal information in your e-mail correspondence with us.
